Wyatt Henderson

SALES MANAGER / WEB DEVELOPER / DATA ENTRY SPECIALIST

Details

2262247947 henderson.wyatt95@gmail.com

Links

My Portfolio Website
https://wjwhportfoliopage.netlify.app

Skills

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

C# .NET

React

SQL

Direct Sales

B2B Sales

Communication Skills

Fast Typing Skills

Business Development

Management

Hobbies

Skiing, Golfing, Game Building, Basketball

Profile

Self-motivated individual who spent 4-years developing my communication and strategy skills in the Direct Marketing industry. Passionate for learning new things I have taught myself full-stack development through online resources over the last 2-years. My goal is to work in Software Development.

Employment History

Data Entry / Payment Processing Admin, FCT, London

AUGUST 2019 - PRESENT

• Serve as a positive and enthusiastic member of the team while going above and beyond expectations to ensure department success.

Business Development Specialist, Compudata Systems Inc, London

• Transformed the sales funnel to allow for more calls per hour leading to a higher number of prospective leads.

Outbound Small Business Consultant, Bill Gosling Outsourcing, London APRIL 2018 – AUGUST 2018

 Utilized my prior knowledge of direct sales to bring in steady numbers for the success of the business.

Independent Contractor (Insurance Representative), Combined Insurance, Thamesford

DECEMBER 2017 - APRIL 2018

• Passed my certification for A&S insurance and worked closely with the Regional Sales Manager to organize soft market trips and training strategies.

Team Leader / Area Manager / Regional Sales Manager, Hamilton Tech Drive Inc, Hamilton / Halifax / London

MARCH 2016 - NOVEMBER 2017

- Earned massive respect from the existing team as one of the top sales reps within a 2-month time frame.
- Excelled by being promoted to an Area Manager within 5-months and then to a Regional Manager after 1-year.

Sales Rep / Team Leader / Field Manager, Global Faces Direct, Kitchener / Hamilton / London

OCTOBER 2014 - MARCH 2016

 Dedicated to the company and the success of our location rapidly became the top representative for the Kitchener location and one of the top representatives for the country.

Education

Diploma, Rossland Secondary School, Rossland, BC SEPTEMBER 2008 – AUGUST 2013

First Year Metal Fabrication, Nelson Selkirk College, Nelson, BC

Upgrading, Wheable Continuing Education, London, ON NOVEMBER 2018 – JULY 2019

Courses

Responsive Web Design, FreeCodeCamp.Org

References

References available upon request

Awards

Optimist Clud, Ralph Mainprize Optimist Award, London, ON

JULY 2019